Guide to the Buildings and Grounds collection A1000
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- West Hall
  - Photographs - Interiors and exteriors
    - Front views of East and West Halls (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, corner view, hedges and people on steps (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, top view (looking down on building) (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Side view of West Hall covered in ivy (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Colgate Quadrangle, West Hall, trees, and paths (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall front view with ivy and trees (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall in the winter with people walking (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall in the shadows (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, back view, obscured by trees (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, back view, only half of building shown (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - East and West Halls in winter, 1967 January (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall interior room (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall front view with balconies, ivy, and trees (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall side view with large pine tree (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall in the winter with trees and snow (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall in the winter, with hedges and trees covered in snow (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, back view with flag pole (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, front view with one tree (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, side view, completely covered in ivy (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall front view on cardboard (brown and white picture) (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, corner view with balconies and hedges (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Alumni, East, and West Halls, copy of an old picture, circa 1860 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Looking down on the campus from afar (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall interior, fireplace, chairs, and tables (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, side view, faded picture (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall, view of the steps leading up to the door (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall side view with ivy and hedges (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall interior with chairs and tables (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall interior, blurry image (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West Hall lounge (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - West hall, student in his room (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Back view of West Hall, East Hall, and Alumni (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Willow Path
  - Photographs, circa 1910-1937; 13 items (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, circa 1912, 1930-1945; 28 items (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1922-1945; 38 items (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, circa 1910-1980; 33 items (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Bridge, circa 1915-1945; 37 items (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Planting and replacement of willows, 1930, 1989; 9 items (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - E.H. Stone - Photos from negatives, undated; 30 items (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Large photographs, circa 1930, circa 1940, undated; 5 items (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Whitnall Field
  - History and Photographs, 1927, 1946, 1964; 24 items (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Whitnall Field (Old), undated; 8 items (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Whitnall Field (New) - Football Scoreboard, 1966; 1 item (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Wynn Hall
  - Wynn Hall, 1979; 13 items (Box 73, Folder 4)